

PABLO BRANCOLI

Software Engineer | Data Scientist

- pbrancoli@uc.cl
- **J** +569 79873658
- Santiago, Chile
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/pablo-brancoli-0aa8191b7/
- **PORTFOLIO** https://github.com/Brocoleta

TECHNOLOGIES

ABOUT ME

Python

Typescript

Google Cloud

ML Python

AWS

Deep Learning

React

Firebase

Power BI

Excel

Young student of Civil Engineering with a specialization in Computer Science and Data Science, passionate about providing efficient solutions through the use of advanced technologies and applying knowledge of Machine Learning and Data Science.

EDUCATION

Civil Engineering in Computer Science with specialization in Data Science | Pontifical Catholic University of Chile

1 03/2018 - 07/2023

Santiago, Chile

INTERESTS

Artificial Intelligence

Open Al

Camping

Trekking

Football

Physics

High School Education | San Benito School

1 04/2004 - 12/2017

Santiago, Chile

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native **English: Advanced**

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer and Data Scientist | Sundes Collection

1 04/2021 - 07/2023

Santiago, Chile

- Worked on cloud development projects using Google Cloud Platform and Firebase, achieving punctual and efficient deliveries.
- Designed and implemented a Machine Learning model to predict house prices.

Scout Leader | Scout Group Santiago

= 04/2018 - 07/2021

- Santiago, Chile
- Managed and oversaw the finances of the 200-member group, optimizing resources and ensuring participation in key events.

PROJECTS

Data Science Portfolio



 Portfolio of Data Science/Engineer applications, using AWS services such as S3, EC2, LAMBDA, ATHENA, and others like Apache Airflow or SnowFlake. More information in the repository's readme: https://github.com/Brocoleta/Brocoleta



• Conducted a study on targeted attacks on recommendation systems, biasing their results in favor or against certain elements. The link to the document is available in the repository.